[Music]
welcome back hope you're having a good
morning The Last Promise let's get
straight to all the top stocks that
we're tracking for you and Sonia you're
going up first up uh tell us uh adani
group there's a clarification that's
come about oh absolutely so the adani
group has put out a clarification on the
exchanges with regards to the report
that was published by the Ken yesterday
and they have strongly refuted all the
allegations made in that particular
report now there are some important
clarifications the group says that they
have completed a full prepayment of the
margin linked share-backed financing and
that Aggregates to over two billion
dollars so a complete repayment has been
done which is a big positive all
corresponding shares that have been
pledged for those facilities have now
been released so they have released all
corresponding shares as Perth March 12th
media note
um they also talk about how all
sharebacked facilities Avail by the
promoters have now been paid off which I
think could provide some relief to the
stocks as well the list Co pledged
positions for adani green adani Port
sadani transmission and Enterprises have
all reduced substantially so the pledge
shares have reduced substantially in
fact they have given details of the
pledges and how much they've reduced it
they've released 1.9 crores of adani
Enterprises promoter pledges as of March
6th they've released a six and a half
crores worth of adani ports pledges
they've released 2.8 crores of adani
transmission promoter plaid shares as
well and adani green has made a
disclosure as well of two and a half
crores of shares released so a lot of
this is positive news flow and I expect
the stocks to be in the green today some
relief rally there okay all right so
that's about the adani group I'm looking
at vedanta remember Hindustan Singh
declared a big dividend and the Hope was
that maybe in fact vedanta limited
they'll pass through all of that and the
hope is that they'll declare anything
between 19 rupees store or 90 rupees 20
price say worth of dividend they've gone
ahead and they've output that so they've
declared their fifth internal dividend
20 rupees 50 prices for the year fiscal
year it's more than 100 rupees the total
payout from this dividend will be more
than 7 600 crores odd and out of that
remember the promoter entity which holds
nearly around 70 has taken the company
will get bulk of it that requested
nearly around 600 million USD now that's
helpful because vedanta is resources
just a month or so ago everyone's
talking about a default at least in the
near term they'll be able to meet their
near-term obligations so expect the
stock to open up in the green so
yesterday as well it was a relative
outperformer let's talk about another
stock I say I say Lombard survey joins
us to fill us in on details of that one
should be
ICICI Lombard is in Focus today because
it's held its digital day some key
takeaways from that meet are that it is
going to use Tech to focus on product
Innovation and building unique
distribution channels to increase
penetration the management did say that
the tech Spence has a one and a half to
two percent impact on combined ratio but
it is also driving premium growth and
new partner integration the iot models
for risk management in the SME space has
increased customers by close to one and
a half times in fy23 versus what it was
in FY 19. the IL take care app has
crossed 4.5 million downloads and it has
led to a 2.4 Times Higher hit rate in
Ford fraud detection in fy23 the app is
also driving 12 times savings on its
claims the management has reiterated its
guidance of achieving a 102 combined
ratio over the next two years a
brokerages have a neutral outlook on the
stock JP Morgan has a neutral rating
with a Target price of 12.50 more when
Stanley has an overweight rating with a
Target price of 1400 and nuama has a
hold rating with a Target price of 1280.
all right survey thanks very much for
that two more names map my India and
zf's steering Vivek has got details
well you know two large block deals that
we are tracking you know map my India
yesterday I saw a significant chunk of a
shareholding actually getting uh
exchanged by the block deal so one of
the earlier investors of the company a
japanese-based company by the name of
zendrin actually sold one and a half
percent stake in the company and at the
end of the December quarter they held
almost 6.16 company remember you know
zendron is a japanese-based digital
mapping firm that actually aided the
growth of mapinda prior to the IPO as
well also keep an ad for ZF Steering you
know a significant block happening over
there as well so Robert Bosch Automotive
you know has exited its entire
25.79 stake in the company and this was
done at 400 rupees this year two of the
already existing promoters have uptastic
so Dinesh Munoz you know purchased ten
and a half percent stake in the company
already owning ten and a half persons
take at the end of the December quarter
and another promoter by the name of
utkash Munoz helps further purchased 15
and a half percent stake having held
almost 13.13
company at the end of the December
quarter
okay thanks a lot for that well uh Nigel
you're watching out for JSL and rhi
magnesita yeah let's start off with
Rachel and magnesia I remember in
February itself they said that they're
looking at raising money by Equity to
the tune of front fifteen hundred crore
rupees and the street didn't like that
now there's some encouraging news
because at least the promoter entity
will be participating in that and out of
that 1500 Crew at least 200 crores is
likely to come from them because they've
scheduled a board meeting out there so
I'll view this news as possibly some
part of the equity race that uh we
already have those details now next up
you're looking at JSL stainless well
they've entered into collaboration
agreement with the company in Indonesia
and that's for construction and
operation of a nickel pig iron or
smelter facility in Indonesia the total
amount they could be investing is around
157 million dollars and they'll be
taking closer on 49 stake out there the
key reason that they're doing this is to
assure themselves for some amount of
their raw material availability because
nickel is used to produce stainless so
you know the street is a little bit
divided on this one but I'm going with
green because it seems the stock is
already directed a good respect from the
recent Peak valuation-wise as well there
is some support so going with green on
this one all right well let's go across
to sonal now she has some more stocks in
the news that she's watching this
morning uh sonal good morning good
morning Sonia let me start with SML
Isuzu effective first of April after we
have heard of these price hikes across
the auto companies SML Isuzu will be
hiking price of trucks by four percent
and buses by six percent so that stock
is in Focus nbcc has won work orders
worth the 146 crore rupees uh we also
have pnb housing they have approved the
rights issue that they had declared
earlier so it will be a rights issue of
nine could have fully paid up Equity
shares each for an amount aggregating to
2500 crore rupees
okay thanks a lot for that so let's do a
quick recap of our top stocks and focus
talks with positive news flow adani
group stocks after the clarification
that came out on the exchanges
steering rhi magnesita Jindal stainless
SML Isuzu nbcc and pnb Housing Finance
while the only stock with negative news
flow today is CE info systems uh so
let's see how that one plays out but
let's also watch out for what's
happening in the world of crude uh three
days of an up move is what we're seeing
this is some recovery uh coming through
Manisha Gupta is joining in for a
Roundup of all the action there Manisha
good morning
morning Sonia thank you for that well we
are trading at a two-week highest for
the crude oil prices you've seen four
percent of gain in this week and we are
inching close to that 80 a barrel Mark
yet again will the U.S food inventories
may see a sharp decline by six million
barrels is the latest trigger coming in
for the food prices and then we have
seen exports halted from Turkey the
nuclear war from Russia is adding the
geopolitical premium as well and the
markets are looking at strong Chinese
man for the first quarter that is what
the final numbers are expected to show
and they're not just uh the Brent and
the WTI but the Russian urals also have
rebounded from its two-year load as
China and India demand continues to be
quite strong we are seeing support from
the metal prices also so whether it's
aluminum or zinc both of these Metals in
Asia are right now trading nearly a
percentage point on the higher side and
with the rebound in many of these
Commodities and decline in dollar there
is support that you are seeing in rubber
that one is trading at a two-week eyes
sugar prices trading at a four week
highs as well so cross Commodities there
is some buying opportunities seen in
Asia
all right Manisha thanks very much uh
for that well we'll take a very quick
break here up next David choksi will be
joining us for some stock talk later
we'll also connect with Anil Gupta of
Kei Industries to discuss their business
after going forward stay tuned both
those conversations up next
[Music]
foreign